Five, four, three two, one.
Ready or not, here I come.
Hey, Dad?
Dad.
You'll stay with Aunt May and
Uncle Ben for a little while.
- I wanna go with you.
- No.
Doesn't like crust on
his sandwiches and
he likes to sleep with
a little light on.
- Mary. Come on, come on.
- Oh, God.
Dad.
Be good.
Sorry.
Morning, Flash.
Good morning, Parker.
Hey. It's Peter, right?
I really like your photos.
Oh, thanks. Thanks.
Listen are you busy Friday night?
Cool. Can you take pictures
of my boyfriend's car?
You know, I really wanna frame
a good one for his birthday.
That's really nice of you. Wow,
that's such a nice thought.
Yeah, I'll have a
look at the old...
- The old schedule.
- Okay.
- Parker.
- Yes, sir?
You want to keep that skateboard?
- Yeah.
- Keep it off the ground.
- Sure. Yeah.
- Wheels up.
Like that?
- That's it.
- Okay.
♪ Is there no way down from this ♪
♪ Peak to solid ground ♪
♪ Without having our ♪
♪ Gold teeth pulled
from our mouths ♪
Eat it. Eat it. Eat it.
Eat it. Eat it.
Eat your vegetables,
Gordon. Come on.
Come on.
Hey, Parker, come on.
Get a picture of this.
No, I'm not gonna take a picture
of it. Put him down, man.
- Come on.
- Gordon, don't eat it.
Take the picture.
Put him down, Flash.
Put him down, Eugene.
Hey, man.
Come on.
Get up, Parker.
Get up.
Come on. Come on.
Still not taking the picture.
Stay down, Parker.
Who wants one more?
- One more.
- Flash.
Flash we still on for
after school today?
My house, 3:30?
I hope you did homework.
Last time, I was
disappointed in you.
- Okay, move.
- No, how about we go to class?
How about it?
Whatever.
I thought that was
great what you did.
It was stupid but it was great.
You should go to the nurse.
You might have a concussion.
What's your name?
You don't know my name?
No, I know your name.
I want to know if
you know your name.
Peter.
- Parker. Peter Parker.
- Okay. Okay, good.
I'd still go to the nurse though.
You're Gwen, right?
Gwen Stacy.
All right.
Hey.
I'm making spaghetti
and meatballs tonight.
You're serious? Spaghetti
and meatballs.
Since when don't you like
spaghetti and meatballs, huh?
- Oh, my God.
- What's up?
What happened to your face?
I'm all right. Just,
I fell, skating.
It's all right.
Ben Parker, don't you even
think about leaving that
filthy box in my kitchen.
My bowling trophies.
Oh, well, then, by all means
leave that box in my kitchen.
- What happened to you?
- He fell.
Why you kids ride those
things, I'll never know.
Because it's stupid and dangerous.
Remember when we were stupid?
No.
- Trust me, we were.
- All right. Good to know.
Where's the flood?
Follow me. I'll show you.
- You serious?
- Yes.
All right.
It's the condenser tray.
Too much water for the condenser
tray or the heat exchange tubing.
This has got to be the fill line.
That's the only thing
that makes any sense.
Can you fix it?
No, not tonight. I'll go by
the hardware store tomorrow.
Good deal. And meanwhile,
put this on your face.
How's the other guy look?
Come on. I know a right
cross when I see one.
Yes or no? Do I have to
call somebody's father?
No, no.
All right.
Well, I wouldn't
tell your Aunt May.
I pity the poor kid who'd
have to suffer her wrath.
Before you come up, see if there's
anything else worth saving.
Okay.
- Plumbers don't fix appliances.
- Yes, they do.
They fix pipes and pump things.
If you ask them to...
I forgot all about that thing.
It was your dad's.
- Yeah.
- He asked us to keep it safe.
He saw it in the window of that
leather shop over on 9th Avenue.
He was 19. What does a 19-year-old
kid need with a briefcase?
And guess who sold it to him.
- I don't know.
- Your mother.
That's how they met.
He asked you to keep this safe?
There's nothing in here.
Have you looked?
There's nothing here.
Your father was a very
secretive man, Peter.
Yeah, I know.
Who's that?
Do you know who that is?
Some guy who worked
with your dad, I guess.
Just take this off the
table, all right?
We're gonna eat. Off.
And wash your hands.
- Now.
- All right.
Go on.
I need you to be a good boy.
Where are you going?
There's something your
mum and I have to do.
What is this?
"Zero, zero, decay
rate algorithm."
Yeah, one sec, one sec.
Come in.
You okay?
- Yeah. What's up?
- Oh, my God.
You look just like him.
- Can I come in?
- Yeah.
Listen I don't have
much education.
You know that, Peter.
Hell, I stopped being able to help
with your homework
when you were 10.
What I'm trying to say is,
I know it's been rough for
you without your dad.
And I know we don't
talk much about them.
- Yeah, it's all right.
- No, it is not all right.
I wish I could change
it, but I can't.
Curt Connors.
That's the name of the guy in
the picture with your dad.
They worked together for
years and they were close.
But after that night,
we never saw him again.
He never even called.
Not once.
Go figure.
She's pretty.
Uncle Ben.
What?
You're a pretty great dad.
Excuse me.
What?
Can I help you?
I don't know. I'm here
to see Dr Connors.
Right.
You'll find yourself to the left.
You are here for the internship?
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
You'll find your
badge to the left.
Having trouble finding yourself?
No. Yeah, I got it.
Okay...
Mr Guevara.
Thanks.
Welcome to Oscorp.
Born from the mind of our
founder, Norman Osborn,
the Oscorp Tower houses
108 floors of innovation.
Our scientific minds
are pushing the
boundaries of defence, biomedical,
and chemical technologies.
The future lies within.
Welcome to Oscorp.
I'm Gwen Stacy, a senior
at Midtown Science,
and head intern to Dr Connors.
I'll be with you for the
duration of your visit.
Where I go, you go.
That's the rule. Remember
that all will be fine.
Come on.
- If you forget that...
- Listen.
Look, listen.
Tell them Rodrigo Guevara is here.
Just tell them Rodrigo
Guevara is here.
My name's Rodrigo.
I guess I don't need to tell you
what happens if you forget.
Shall we?
Come around this way.
Good afternoon, Gwen.
Dr Connors.
Welcome.
My name is Dr Curtis Connors.
Yes, in case you're
wondering, I'm a southpaw.
I'm not a cripple,
I'm a scientist, and the world's
foremost authority on herpetology.
That's reptiles, for those
of you who don't know.
Like the Parkinson's patient who
watches on in horror as her
body slowly betrays her, or the
man with macular degeneration
whose eyes grow dimmer each
day, I long to fix myself.
I want to create a world
without weakness.
Anyone care to venture
a guess just how?
Yes.
Stem cells?
Promising. But the solution
I'm thinking of is more radical.
- No one?
- Cross-species genetics.
Person gets Parkinson's,
when the brain cells
that produce dopamine,
start to disappear.
But a zebra fish has the ability
to regenerate cells on command.
If you could give this ability
to the woman you're talking
about, that's that. She's...
She's curing herself.
Yeah, you just have to look
past the gills on her neck.
And you are?
He's one of Midtown Science's
- best and brightest.
- Really?
Second in his class.
- Second?
- Yeah.
Sure about that?
I'm pretty sure.
I'm afraid duty calls.
I'll leave you in
the more-than-capable
hands of Miss Stacy.
Nice meeting you all.
If you'd like to gather round.
Welcome to Oscorp's tree of life.
Our planet's tree
of life is immense.
At Oscorp's
- Cross-Species Division...
- Hi.
We endeavour to explore
exciting new methods...
What are you doing, "Rodrigo"?
Oh, yeah.
What are you doing here?
I work here. I don't.
I was gonna say I work here,
but it seems like you do work
here. So you know that I don't.
You following me?
No, I'm not following you, no.
I had no idea you worked here.
Why would you be here?
I just snuck in because
I love science.
- You love it.
- I'm passionate about it.
So you snuck in?
- I have to lead this tour group.
- I know.
I'll ask you more about this
later. Do not get me in trouble.
- I promise you I won't.
- Stay with the group.
All right, guys? I'm gonna take
you to the bioreactor room now.
Sorry. Yo.
Sorry.
We received the results from the
mRNA sequences this morning.
They were disappointing.
Define "disappointing."
Another dead end.
It's the decay rate algorithm.
- And this is to be expected.
- Expected?
You said you were close.
We are close, but
it's gonna take time.
He doesn't have time.
Norman Osborn is
dying, Dr Connors.
Save him.
Or we'll both lose our heads.
All right, give me the badge.
Give it to me.
Sorry.
Disgusting. Now I smell like beer.
I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't mean to, I
didn't... I didn't...
Get your hand off her.
I'm trying to get my...
Are you kidding?
I'm sorry.
Are you kidding me?
- Hey, get him, Rudy.
- Hey.
Man, I'm sorry.
Man, are you all right?
- Take him down.
- Come on.
Get him, man. Get him.
No, man, no. Not my board.
Please, dude, don't...
Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Coney Island, next stop.
Next and final stop, Coney Island.
Hey.
Hey. Hey.
Sorry. I'm late.
- I got...
- We've been so worried.
I know. I'm sorry.
Watch out.
That's a fly, Peter.
Yeah.
I'm so sorry I kept you guys up,
I'm insensitive, I'm irresponsible
and I'm hungry.
Meatloaf.
Drinking?
What's this?
I don't think so.
This is your meatloaf.
This beats all other meat loafs.
Something is very wrong.
Yeah.
Nobody likes your meatloaf.
I got it.
He took the frozen
macaroni and cheese.
I noticed that.
Why didn't you tell me you
didn't like my meatloaf?
You could have said that
to me 37 years ago.
How many meat loafs
have I made for you?
♪ It was all his fault ♪
♪ Introduced me to know-it-all ♪
♪ And the cannibal ♪
♪ Oh, well by the
time they started ♪
♪ Showing up I ran the
risk of blowing up ♪
♪ These times, these
times get tough ♪
♪ So if I stay ♪
♪ We're gonna see
who's had enough ♪
Peter.
What are you doing up there?
Homework.
Be careful.
Sure.
Dr Connors.
You don't remember me. I...
The intern from the other day.
Yeah, yeah. That's right, yeah.
I'm sure you're very nice,
but this is a home.
I ask you to make an
appointment with my office.
I'm Richard Parker's son.
Peter?
I'm afraid I can't help
you much. I don't know
why they left or where
they were going.
Good reflexes.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- I read your book.
Yeah.
It's something, you know.
So you really think it's possible,
cross-species genetics?
Yes, of course.
Your father and I were
mocked for our theories.
Not just in the community at
large, but at Oscorp, as well.
They called us mad scientists.
And then your father bred the
spiders and everything changed.
The results were
beyond encouraging.
They were spectacular.
We were gonna change
the lives of millions.
Including my own.
Then it was over.
He was gone.
Took his research with him.
And I knew without him, I...
I...
I was angry.
So I stayed away from
you and your family.
And for that, I'm truly sorry.
Say...
Say it worked.
Say you got it to work.
Like, how much would the
foreign species take over?
What could the side effects be?
It's hard to say, considering
no subject survived.
The problem was always...
The decay rate algorithm?
- Right.
Can I?
Of course.
Extraordinary.
How did you come up with this?
Peter, how about coming
to see me at the Tower
- one day after school?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Number one, Reggie.
Run it, buddy.
Let's go. Reggie-
Rejected.
You did that on purpose, Flash.
I should've. You better
watch your back.
Hey.
All right?
Give it up.
Come on, man.
One sec.
- Come on, man.
- Why don't you take it from me?
That's right. Take it.
Go ahead. Take it.
Just take it.
All right, how about this?
All right?
How about that?
- Come on, Flash.
- Flash, stop playing, man.
- Take it from him.
- Come on, Flash. Take it.
Yo, Flash, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Do it, Flash.
- Stop playing, man.
- Let's go, Flash.
- What are you doing?
- What's up?
What you doing?
All right, bring it. Come
on, Parker. Come on.
Peter's behaviour is
just unacceptable.
They won't make us pay
for the backboard.
I don't care about the backboard.
- Was that true?
- What?
What I heard in there just now.
Did you humiliate that boy?
Yeah, I did.
- But...
- But what?
- This guy deserved it.
- Did he?
- Yeah.
- Is he the kid that hit you?
Is he?
Yeah, yeah, but...
So all this is about getting even.
If so, I guess you
must feel pretty
good about yourself now, right?
Am I right or wrong?
Yeah, I thought so.
Well, thanks to this
little escapade of yours,
I had to change shifts at work,
so you have to pick up Aunt May
tonight at 9:00. Understood?
- Is that understood?
- Yeah.
Okay, good.
She looks familiar.
The girl on your computer.
Yeah.
He's got you on his computer.
I'm his probation officer.
Don't forget Aunt May.
Okay.
He's a character.
That's my uncle.
He's a pathological liar.
He thought you were someone else.
Oh, man, you don't have
me on your computer?
I took a photo of the debate team,
and you're in the debate team.
- Right.
- So,
he must have seen I was
touching up stuff.
- Touching up stuff?
- Come on.
I was I'm not gonna answer that.
- Did you get expelled?
- No, no.
I didn't get expelled. I
got community service.
So you want to I don't know?
Want to what?
I don't know.
Just...
I don't know. We could...
We could do something
else, or we could...
If you don't feel
like, we could...
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, either one.
- Really?
- Sure.
Okay.
All right, good. Sounds good.
Cool.
Okay.
I can't right now,
I can't right now.
Yeah, no.
- I'm so busy right now.
- I know, me too.
But maybe...
- Yeah, just, you know...
- Some other...
- Time, all right.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- All right.
♪ Let me in ♪
♪ Unlock the door ♪
♪ I've never felt
this way before ♪
♪ And the wheels just ♪
♪ Keep on turning ♪
♪ The drummer ♪
♪ Begins to drum ♪
♪ I don't know which way ♪
♪ I'm going ♪
♪ I've come ♪
♪ For you I'd wait ♪
♪ 'Til kingdom come ♪
♪ Until my days ♪
♪ My days ♪
♪ Are done ♪
♪ And say you'll come ♪
♪ And set me free ♪
♪ Just say you'll wait ♪
♪ You'll wait for me ♪
♪ Say you'll wait ♪
Whoo.
♪ You'll wait ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Just say you'll wait ♪
♪ You'll wait for me ♪
We have protein structure, rDNA,
chromatography,
transgenics testing,
that's X-ray video. That's the
only one on the planet. We have
- human line testing over...
- I remember that.
I've seen that before.
The Ganali device.
Yeah, I remember a picture
of that in my dad's office.
The idea was so simple. You
load it with an antigen.
It creates a cloud
which can be dispersed
over a neighbourhood, even a city.
Theoretically, you could
cure polio in an afternoon.
That's incredible.
Well, others
disagreed. What if the
device were loaded with a toxin?
What if you wanted to
opt out? You can't
run away from a cloud after all,
so here it lies, gathering dust.
What you see here is a
computer model of a lizard.
Many of these wonderful creatures
have so brilliantly adapted,
that they can regenerate
entire limbs at will.
You can imagine my envy.
We're trying to harness
this capability
and transfer it into
our host subject:
Freddy the three-legged mouse.
Enter the algorithm now.
Need to take that?
System ready for gene insertion.
Okay.
Check.
See what I'm trying to do?
- Pre-empt the proteins.
- The immune response.
Beginning trials.
Pending. Pending.
Failed. Subject deceased.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Pending.
Failed.
Pending. Failed.
Subject deceased. Pending.
Peptide algorithm accepted.
Regrowth complete.
- Hey.
- Vitals normal.
Blood pressure normal.
Limb regeneration successful.
Extraordinary.
And thank you.
Meet Fred and Wilma our
three-legged mice.
Here you go.
Hey buddy. I got you.
Okay.
Careful, don't want to
stick you by mistake.
Human trials aren't
until next week.
There.
Hey.
Hey, I thought you...
Didn't you forget something?
What?
Now, don't answer that, but I'm
glad to know it's working.
You owe your aunt an
apology big time.
Be a man.
Get in there and apologise.
I'm sorry, Aunt May, I...
Honestly, you don't have
to apologise to me. It's your...
- The hell he doesn't.
- Ben.
Look, I'm sorry, I got distracted.
- Oh, he got distracted.
- Yeah.
Your aunt, my wife, had
to walk 12 blocks alone
in the middle of
the night and then
wait in a deserted subway station,
because you got distracted.
Ben, sweetheart, honestly,
I am completely capable
of walking home...
You will not defend this boy.
- I'm not defending...
- You are.
- Listen to me, son.
- Yeah, go ahead.
You're a lot like your father.
You really are, Peter,
and that's a good thing,
but your father lived by a
philosophy, a principle, really.
He believed that if you could do
good things for other people,
you had a moral obligation
to do those things.
That's what's at stake here.
Not choice.
Responsibility.
That is nice. That's great.
That's all well and
good. So where is he?
- What?
- Where is he?
Where's my dad?
He didn't think it was
his responsibility
to be here to tell me himself?
Oh, come on, how dare you?
How dare I? How dare you?
Where you going?
Peter, come back here, please.
Ben, leave him alone for a little
while. He'll be all right.
Peter.
Peter?
It's $2.07.
Yeah. No, I know.
Yeah, you're holding
up the line. No.
You can leave a penny,
you can't take a penny.
- What?
- You can leave
a penny anytime, you
have to spend 10 dollars
to take a penny.
It's store policy.
- You're holding up my line.
- I don't have 2 cents.
You can't afford milk, step aside.
Daddy didn't give you
enough milk money today?
We're talking about 2 cents.
Just step aside, kid.
Really?
Yo, not cool, bro.
Hey, man, stop.
Somebody stop that guy.
Hey, kid, little help?
Not my policy.
Somebody stop that dude.
Hey.
Hey, stop.
Somebody stop that dude.
Hey.
Oh, God, oh, God.
Uncle Ben, Uncle Ben.
Call an ambulance.
Someone call an ambulance.
Uncle Ben, Uncle Ben.
Oh, God, oh, my God.
On, God.
No.
Oh, Jesus.
Witnesses gave a
description to the
sketch artist. I need
you to take a look.
No, I don't know him.
I didn't expect you would,
ma'am. Homicide detectives
are on it. We'll see
what they turn up.
Okay.
Can I have that?
Sure.
There's one other thing. He has a
star tattooed on his left hand.
Peter, I know things have
been difficult lately
and I'm sorry about that.
I think I know what
you're feeling.
Hey, Parker.
- Not today.
- Come on, I just want to talk.
It feels better, right?
Look, your uncle died.
I'm sorry.
I get it.
Okay?
Peter.
Stay away from him.
- You understand?
- Hey.
- Stay away from Joey.
You like beating on girls?
You like beating on old men?
Hey, pal keep walking.
- You're in the wrong place.
- When were you in Queens?
- I asked you a question.
- Nicky, no.
That the gun? You
gonna kill me too?
- Hey.
- Stop it.
- Get off.
Wait, oh, don't hit Nicky.
Back up.
This guy is crazy.
Get him.
Get back here, man. Get him.
Follow him.
- Go around, man.
- I'll follow you.
Go, go, go.
There he is.
Can't get away.
He has a star tattooed
on his left hand.
Oh, yeah?
Come on.
I know what you look like.
You hear me?
I've seen your face.
Is that all you got?
Just take it, take it.
Engineered from genetically
enhanced spiders,
Oscorp's BioCable
tensile strength is
unparalleled. We're just beginning
to understand all the potential
industrial applications.
A single pellet can safely
store several hundred metres
of the lightweight cable.
Mother...
Attention, all units
in the confines
of Precinct 13, receiving a 10-30
on West 19th Street and Broadway.
Assailant is Caucasian
male, mid-30s,
170 to 180 pounds,
shoulder-length blond hair.
Last seen on foot heading
eastbound on 19th Street.
Hey.
You got a description?
Well, no, he wears a mask.
A mask?
Most of his victims
are suspects with
serious rap sheets.
They're calling him a vigilante.
Okay, he's not a vigilante,
he's an anarchist.
Help me, somebody. Arrest me.
Get me out of here.
Hey, look.
Spandex. Spandex.
Everything spandex.
Extraordinary velocity
vector is a function
of both mass and acceleration.
Come on, you know
better than anyone,
the weight on any pendulum
has no effect on speed.
It doesn't affect frequency, but
it's totally a factor in momentum.
Hey, Aunt May.
Yeah. Eggs?
Organic, got it.
In the future, if you're
gonna steal cars,
don't dress like a car thief, man.
What are you? You a cop?
Really? You seriously
think I'm a cop?
Cop in a skin-tight
red-and-blue suit?
You know, you're...
You've got a mind of
the true scholar, sir.
I was going more for the
guys who do the luge.
Good thinking.
Get out the window.
There you go. You got it.
Crotch.
- Just let me go.
- Is that a real knife?
Yes, it's a real knife.
My weakness, it's small knives.
Just let me go.
Anything but knives.
Oh, it's so simple.
- That was cool.
- What is this?
Webbing I developed. I don't
think you want to know.
Let me go.
Okay, one second.
Hold on, one second.
Knock it off, man. No.
Come on, let me go. Stop it.
That isn't funny.
- It is kind of funny.
- Help.
This could've gone a lot worse.
Now hold still.
Boys in blue here.
- Yo, I got him.
- Freeze.
- He's not going anywhere.
- Don't move.
You serious?
Who are you?
No one grasps the
concept of the mask.
Freeze.
I just did 80 percent of your job.
And that?
That's how you repay me?
Hold it right there.
Well, that was fun.
Bus. Hey there, everybody.
What are you doing?
Hey, watch out.
I'm swinging here.
So 38 of New York's finest
versus one guy in a unitard.
Am I correct?
You don't have to wait up for me.
- Yes, I do.
- No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
- Okay.
- Where were you?
I was out.
Did you get the eggs?
Nope. Forgot the eggs.
I'm gonna get them now.
No, you most certainly will not.
Not at this hour.
Look at me, Peter.
Take off the damn
hood and look at me.
Peter. Where did you go?
Who does this to you?
Please go to sleep, Aunt May.
- Please tell me.
- Aunt May, please
please, please go to sleep.
I can't sleep. Don't you
understand? I can't sleep.
Peter, listen to me.
Secrets have a cost.
They're not for free.
Not now, not ever.
Cross-species genetics
is finally working.
I've used the lizard DNA to
help Freddy regrow that limb.
It's a miracle.
No, it's hard work and promise.
It's a step closer
to the primate lab.
He doesn't have time
for every little step.
Little?
I just mean he can't wait.
Well, he'll have to.
Unless he wants to be a lab rat.
That's not what I'm saying...
So, what are you saying?
You have to start human trials.
Now.
No, I don't, and no, I won't.
- Well, then he's going to die.
- People die.
Even Norman Osborn.
We are not finished.
Human trials?
Where are you going to find
the people to volunteer?
As far as anyone's concerned,
it's for a flu shot.
I might think the Veterans
Hospital is a place to start.
You've gotta be kidding me.
I don't think I am.
It's a little late for
shock and indignation.
About 15 years late.
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
Richard Parker wore it well.
On you, it's a cheap
suit, as it was then.
I had nothing to do with that.
Is that what you told his son?
I don't know what you're saying.
You don't know, or you
don't wanna know?
I'll remind you what happened.
Richard Parker said
just about the same
thing then that you
are saying now.
The clock is ticking, Dr Connors.
I...
I won't.
Fine.
The formula is ours now anyway.
Say goodbye to that arm
you have dreamed of.
I'm shutting you down.
Have your office cleared
out by the morning.
Your toys can be taken
away too, you know.
Right, Freddy?
- Hey.
- Hi.
How's it going?
Where you headed?
- Monday, B track.
- Oh, it's Thursday.
- It's Thursday?
- What happened?
- What?
- Your eye, it looks bruised.
Oh, yeah, no, I don't...
Maybe I got a rash or...
It's bad. Have you
gone to the nurse?
Do you like branzino?
- Like, a fish.
- No, no. I know. I know.
Well, if you want,
you can come to this
address at 8:00 tonight.
My mum's making branzino.
So...
It's apartment, 2016. I
didn't write that part down.
I don't know why I...
- I'll remember it.
- Oh, okay.
2016.
Hi.
How did you get out there?
The fire escape.
Your doorman's intimidating.
It's 20 storeys.
Yeah. It's all right.
- This is your room.
- Yes, this is my room.
Books.
Shoes.
Oh, hey...
I got your mum these.
Oh, lovely.
- Beautiful, right?
- Beautiful.
They were nice.
- No, they're beautiful.
- I'm sorry.
No, it's impressive. They
actually held together very well.
I'm gonna keep these.
You have your suit in there?
My Suit?
It's for dinner. Are you gonna?
Are you gonna wear that?
- That's...
- Hey, hon.
You must be Peter.
Dad, this is Peter.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Nice to meet you.
Dinner's ready.
Hope you like branzino.
Who doesn't?
Emma, it's Curt.
- Is he there?
- I'm afraid not, doctor.
The car is taking him to the
Veterans Hospital in Brooklyn.
No. He can't, Emma.
You have to stop him. He...
I would, but I always
lose him on the bridge.
I'll make sure Dr Ratha returns
your call as soon as possible.
I'm going to Holton Avenue,
across the river. I'm in a hurry.
You want me to take the
tunnel or the bridge?
Bridge. Take the bridge.
All right, we'll do that.
Hey, you all right back there?
You tweaking man?
Just drive.
Okay.
You're having trouble there?
The head goes on the other...
Help Gwen's friend with his fish.
On, I...
I got no idea.
First time.
- Branzino.
- George.
Tell us about your day.
Did you catch that spider guy yet?
No, we didn't catch him yet.
But we will. He's an amateur
who's assaulting civilians
in the dead of night.
He's clumsy, he leaves clues,
but he's still dangerous.
He's assaulting people?
I'm not sure.
I mean, I saw that video, with
him and the car thief, and
I think most people
would say that he was
providing a public service.
Most people would be wrong.
If I wanted the car thief off the
street, he'd already
be off the street.
So why wasn't he then?
Let me illuminate you.
The car thief was leading
us to the people who run
the operation. It's a
six-month-long sting.
It's called strategy. I'm sure
you're aware of the term?
You've heard about that in school?
- Yeah.
- Good.
I know.
- He didn't know you had a plan.
- You seem to know
a lot about this. Know
something we don't?
- Whose side are you on?
- I'm not on anyone's side.
I saw a video on the internet...
You saw the video on the internet.
- Well, then the case is closed.
- Well, no.
If you watch the video...
Maybe send you a link?
It looks like he's trying to help.
On the internet he's being
made out to look like a hero.
No, no.
I'm not saying he's a hero.
- What are you trying to say?
- He's trying to help.
He's trying to do something
the police can't.
Something the police can't?
- I don't know.
- What do you think we do?
Sit around eating doughnuts
with our thumbs
planted up our asses?
- George. George.
- Daddy.
- Up your what?
- Howard.
He stands for what you stand for.
Protecting innocent
people from bad guys.
I stand for law and order.
That's what I stand for.
Okay? I wear a badge.
This guy wears a
mask like an outlaw.
He's hunting down criminals
that all look the same,
like he's got some sort
of personal vendetta.
But he's not protecting
innocent people, Mr Parker.
Let's get some air, Peter.
- Dad, we need to talk.
- Yes, we do.
Thank you for having me. I'm sorry
if I insulted you. It
was not my intention.
You're welcome.
Branzino was real good, Mrs Stacy.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Dad.
- Yeah?
Well, that was something.
I'm sorry. I thought he was going
to arrest me at one point.
No, I wouldn't have
let him arrest you
- What happened to your face?
- I wanna tell you something.
Okay.
I've been bitten...
So have I.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay. I gotta
tell you this one thing.
I gotta tell you this thing about
- the vigilante and the car thief.
- Oh, okay.
What?
- No, no, no.
- I don't want to talk about that.
Forget that. I won't
talk about that.
- I'm gonna talk about me, okay?
- What about you?
It's impo... I wish
I could just...
I can't. It's hard to say.
Just say it.
- I don't know.
- Say it.
What? What?
What?
Okay, then forget it.
You?
- You're Spider-Man.
- Shut up.
Gwen?
Gwen...
Your father wants
you to come inside.
Okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
Gwen.
I'm coming.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Will you please find out
what is going on, Alfred?
Excellent.
Hey.
Hey. What is that?
- Oh, my God.
- I don't know.
Get back in the car.
Help.
Incoming.
Somebody help.
Help me. My kid is trapped.
I want my dad.
Dad.
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Help.
- Hey buddy. It's okay.
- Get away.
- Help.
- Hey, look.
Just a normal guy, all right?
Wanna hold this?
Hold my mask.
All right.
What's your name?
Jack?
- Yes.
- Let's get you out of here.
Okay, stay very still.
All right.
Okay, I got you.
Okay, look.
I'll undo the belt. You hold on
to that seat in front
of you. On three?
- All right.
- Okay, one, two, three.
See how easy that was?
You did a great job.
All right, okay.
Jack, climb now.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
Put it on, the mask.
It's gonna make you strong.
Jack, trust me.
Put it on.
There you go. That's
it. That's it, buddy.
Okay, now, climb.
Come on, Jack.
Do me a favour.
A little faster, okay, bud?
You're doing great, buddy.
You're doing great.
That's it. Keep coming.
Keep it coming.
Keep coming.
No.
Jack. Oh, God.
Thank God.
You okay?
My son. My son.
Oh, my son.
My son.
Who are you?
Spider-Man.
Beautiful.
Settle down, guys.
Settle down, boys. Settle down.
- Come on.
- Listen. At approximately
9 p.m. last night,
an incident took
place on the Williamsburg Bridge.
Much of what occurred
is speculation
at this point. However,
several eyewitnesses
to the crime, as well as our
own preliminary findings, have
positively placed one
individual at the scene.
Which is why, this morning,
I am issuing a warrant
for the masked vigilante
known as Spider-Man.
And lastly, city
council members met
with homeowners and
airport officials,
in the first of four meetings...
It's so beautiful.
Knows how to bite though.
Who else knows about this?
Just you.
Really?
Hey, you don't...
You don't believe what the
police are saying, do you?
Of course not.
Does it scare you?
What you can do?
No.
What did that thing on
the bridge look like?
It was real big. Too
big to be human.
You gotta lay low.
No, can't do that.
You've got to.
I mean, why?
Because of last night.
Those people on the bridge.
Whatever was attacking them
would have killed them.
So I gotta go after it.
That's not your job.
Maybe it is.
I really liked kissing you.
You're an amazing kisser.
Well, you know, it was...
It was good for me too.
Yeah?
Who did that?
Hello.
It's not nice to snoop.
I gave everyone the week off.
Yeah.
Shouldn't you be at school?
No, I got a free track.
I wanted to ask you a question.
How would a predator
track a reptile?
Oh, they don't. Most
reptiles are at the top
of their food chain.
Kings of their domain.
They gotta have vulnerabilities.
Why the sudden interest
in the cold-blooded?
Just asking a question.
I got school stuff.
Biology profiles to do.
So because of the cold blood,
would they react to
changes in temperatures?
You'd have to catch one first.
Did you know there's a rumour
of a new species in New York?
Beautiful and quite large.
What do you know about
it? You seen it?
No, it's not yet classified.
But it can be aggressive,
if threatened.
Doc, you all right?
Never been better, Peter.
Never been better.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Afraid I have to ask you to
leave. I have a new project
I'm working on. I
need to be alone.
Good. Good, good.
Good.
Don't worry, Mr
Parker. I'll be back.
Wonderful things are coming.
Wonderful things.
Fred?
Mr Mayor, if there
was a giant dinosaur
running around you would
be the first to know.
So tell your son he can
rest easy, all right?
Yeah. You and me both, sir.
Okay. Bye-bye.
Mr Parker, why are
you not in school?
- Got a free track.
- Okay, well, I do not.
So make your point quickly.
Fine, there may not be a
dinosaur running around.
There is something more
dangerous, and I know who.
- You know who?
- Dr Curtis Connors.
- He's a biochemist.
- Of Oscorp?
- That's right.
- Dr Connors,
who's my daughter's
mentor. Is that who?
- That's the one.
- Okay.
Recently, Dr Connors gave Gwen
a college recommendation.
It was beautiful. When
I read it, I cried.
You would have me believe that he
is running around dressed
up like a dinosaur?
Not dressing up and
not a dinosaur. He
has transformed himself
into a lizard.
Let me ask you a question.
Do I look like the
Mayor of Tokyo to you?
I'm telling you the
absolute truth.
This man has worked for his whole
life on cross-species genetics.
He lost an arm, he
tried to grow it
back, but the equation
was imbalanced.
He has turned into a lizard.
He's using lizard DNA.
He is dangerous,
and he is planning
something horrific.
I know. I know.
Okay. All right, I get it.
Here's what we'll do.
You'll go back to hanging out
with the citizens of Tokyo.
I'm gonna go back to
protecting the citizens
of this fine, fair city of ours.
Sergeant Butler, please escort
Mr Parker back to school.
Captain Stacy, I'm
not messing around.
Just bring him in. Just call him
in. You have to call him in.
He is a danger to everybody.
- Just, please, listen to me.
- Let's go.
Jimmy.
Get me everything we have
on Dr Curtis Connors.
- Okay? Right away.
- Yeah.
Subject: Dr Curtis Connors.
Current temperature: 89.7.
Steady for 48 hours.
Blood panels reveal lymphocyte
and monocyte readings,
consistent with subject's past.
Clotting rate vastly improved.
Marked enhancement,
in muscle response,
strength and elasticity.
Eyesight similarly improved.
Subject no longer requires
corrective lenses.
This is no longer
about curing ills.
This is about finding perfection.
In attempt to redress
regenerative relapse,
dosage has been increased
to 200 milligrams.
You stopped me once.
You won't stop me again.
I'm getting stronger every day.
Oh, that sucked.
Peter Parker.
Come in.
You should maybe consider
coming in through the lobby.
Also, my father is
under the impression
that you require
psychiatric attention.
Oh, really?
Peter.
What happened?
You should see the other guy.
The other guy, in this instance,
being a giant mutant lizard.
Hey, Gwen, honey.
Do you want cocoa?
Howard's making some.
No, Dad, I do not want cocoa.
Honestly, I'm 17 years old.
Okay.
I remembered somebody
saying her fantasy
was to live in a chocolate house.
Well, that's impractical.
And fattening.
Chocolate house.
- Sorry, Dad.
- It's good.
I can't have cocoa right
now because I'm work...
I'm doing this...
I have cramps.
I feel kind of pukey
and just sort of...
- Like, emotional. I keep crying.
- It's okay. Good.
- Good.
- It's brutal.
You don't want to know.
- It's, like, bad.
- Got it.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- All right.
Easy, bug boy
What'd you call me?
I'm going to be all right.
- No. No.
- Yes. Yes.
I know what this is.
What is it?
Every day, for as long as
I can remember, my father
has left every morning and
he's put a badge on his chest
and strapped a gun to his hip.
And every day, for as
long as I can remember.
I haven't known if he
was gonna make it home.
I got you.
Okay?
I gotta stop him, though.
I have to, because I created him.
What do you mean?
I gave him an equation
that made all of this possible.
Something my father had
been working on, you know.
Secretly. Now I realise
why he kept it a secret.
Point is, this is
my responsibility.
I have to fix it.
Peter.
Hey.
Let's get out of here.
Let's just get out of here.
Just for a minute. Can we?
- No. No.
- Yeah. Yes.
- Yes.
- No.
Yes.
If my parents see me
leaving, I'm dead.
Your parents aren't
gonna see you leaving.
Peter Parker.
Spider-Man.
I'm not the one who needs help.
There will be no more
loneliness, no more outcasts.
Species-wide distribution
could enhance
humanity on an evolutionary scale.
One has to adapt to survive.
"That, changing like the
snake, I might be free
to cast off flesh wherein
I dwell confined."
Would you give it all up after
all you know, you can do?
All the power you feel.
I can save them.
You won't get in the
way of my plan,
Peter Parker.
Go. Go.
Nowhere to hide, Peter.
All these souls lost and alone.
I can save them.
I can cure them.
There's no need to stop me Peter.
You're not thinking straight, Doc.
Stop this. This isn't you.
Let's talk this out.
Doc.
Oh, boy.
You don't want to talk?
There you go.
Don't make me
have to hurt you.
That is disgusting.
Gwen.
I'm gonna throw you
out the window.
What?
Somebody's been a bad lizard.
This is Lieutenant Williams
from the New York City
Police Department. We've got
this building surrounded.
Alpha, let's move ahead. Go.
- Hey.
- Where are you?
I'm fine. I'm okay.
I'm in the sewer,
tracking him. I gotta
stop him before anyone gets hurt.
But we need an antidote.
- Do you know how to run a serum?
- I do it all the time.
Okay, great. Okay, I need
you to go to Oscorp.
I need you to access the
cross-species file.
It's a blue serum. File: 12389.
Okay, got it.
On my way.
I spent my life as
a scientist trying
to create a world without
weakness, without outcasts.
I sought to create a
stronger human being,
but there's no such thing.
Human beings are weak, pathetic,
feeble-minded creatures.
Why be human at all when
we can be so much more?
Faster. Stronger.
Smarter.
This is my gift to you.
Oscorp.
- Captain Stacy.
- What?
We have a confirmed sighting,
sir. The Lizard's headed
- toward Canal Street.
- What about Spider-Man?
Inside the high school.
I want that Spider-Man
off the street.
The lizard creature has
released a biological agent.
All efforts to stop
him have failed
and he is now proceeding
north on 7th Avenue. Over.
- Hi.
- Where are you?
Peter, hi. I'm at Oscorp.
You have to get out of there now.
- The antidote is cooking.
- No, no, no.
Connors is on the way. He's
coming to you right now.
He needs the device. He's
gonna infect the whole city.
Eight minutes left.
You're gonna wait eight minutes
after what I told you?
You leave right now.
That is an order, okay?
I'll get everybody out.
Did you hear what?
Gwen. Gwen. You Mother
Hubbard. Are you serious?
He's heading south.
Stand down now, or
we will open fire.
You are surrounded.
There is no escape.
Go, go.
Clear.
Clear up top.
Clear, sir.
All clear here, sir.
Freeze.
Down on the ground.
Your hands behind your head.
Now.
Parker.
It's headed to Oscorp.
And your daughter's
there right now.
You gotta let me go.
Hold your fire.
Well, Paul, if I didn't see
it, I wouldn't believe it.
I won't venture to say
what it is crawling up
the north side of
the Oscorp Tower,
but clearly it is not human
and it is very, very strong.
Time remaining: one minute.
Antidote complete.
Oh, man.
We're getting the latest
details. This is just coming in.
The New York Police Department
has called for a
city-wide evacuation,
everything south of 54th Street.
If you are south of 54th Street,
you have to move out of
the area immediately.
Spider-Man appears to be
heading towards Oscorp.
He looks injured
and it's really not clear
if he's gonna make it.
That's the guy who saved
my boy on the bridge.
Troy, they're clearing us out.
Something bad's going
down in Midtown.
Still friends with Matthews,
that crane operator on 6th?
- Yeah.
- Get him on the phone for me.
The cops are evacuating everybody.
Get him on the phone for me.
Hey, Charlie, get me
Enrique: on 54th Street.
- You got it.
- Angelo, get your mug over here.
Wolski. You're getting
some overtime.
All tower cranes on 6th,
swing your jib arms over the
avenue Boom angles at 90 degrees.
Spider-Man needs those big
boys high and lined up.
Let's give him a clear
approach. Over.
Come on, Parker.
Hey.
Dad.
I have to get this to Spider-Man.
Get in.
- It can stop the Lizard.
- Get in the car.
- You don't understand.
- Yes, I do.
Your boyfriend is a
man of many masks.
I get it.
Give me this. Get in the car.
Please make sure he's okay.
Initialising Ganali device.
Detonation in T-minus two minutes.
Poor Peter Parker.
No mother, no father, no uncle.
All alone.
He's not alone.
Detonation in T-minus 45 seconds.
Hey.
Gift from Gwen.
I got this, Peter. Go.
T-minus 30 seconds.
Detonation in T-minus 10 seconds.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
No.
The Captain.
Captain.
The Lizard.
It's okay.
We stopped him.
Okay.
Let's get you out
of here. Come on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Look at me. Stay with me.
- Help's on the way, okay?
- You need to...
You need to be gone
when they get here.
Okay?
I'm not going anywhere.
I was wrong about you, Peter.
This city needs you.
Here.
You're gonna need this.
You're gonna make enemies.
People will get hurt.
Sometimes the people
closest to you.
So I want you to promise
me something, okay?
Leave Gwen out of it.
Promise me that.
You promise me.
An eerie calm has set
in over New York City.
Apparently, some sort of
aerosolised antidote
was launched from
Oscorp Tower, which seems to
have counteracted the biotoxins.
Residents of Lower Manhattan
can rest peacefully,
knowing that the
alleged mastermind,
of this terror plot, Dr Curtis
Connors, is behind bars.
We've got John Niles,
on the street for a report
in Lower Manhattan.
John, what do you see?
Sweetheart, it's all right.
It's all right.
Rough night.
It's gonna be all right.
Where have you been?
Hi.
My father died.
There was a funeral.
They shot off rifles and
they made speeches.
Two of my teachers showed up.
And Flash showed up.
Everyone was there but you.
Can't do this. Can't do this.
I'm sorry. I can't...
What are you saying?
I can't see you any more.
I can't.
He made you promise, didn't he?
To stay away from
me, so I'd be safe.
What a pretty girl.
Yeah.
That's what Uncle Ben said.
Did you ask her out?
Why?
Can't.
I'm just no good for her.
Peter Parker, if there's one
thing you are, it's good.
Anyone has a problem with
that can talk to me.
Peter, I know things have been
difficult lately and
I'm sorry about that.
I think I know what
you're feeling.
Ever since you were a little boy,
you've been living with so
many unresolved things.
Well, take it from an old man:
Those things send us down a road.
They make us who we are.
And if anyone's destined for
greatness, it's you, son.
You owe the world your gifts.
You just have to figure
out how to use them.
And know that wherever they
take you, we'll always be here.
So come on home, Peter.
You're my hero.
And I love you.
- What's up, Parker?
- What's up?
Hey. How's it going?
You coming along, man?
Cool shirt.
Yeah.
Dude's crazy.
But chicks dig him.
Come on, guys, you heard
the bell. Get to class.
I had a professor once who
liked to tell his students,
that there were only 10 different
plots in all of fiction.
Well, I'm here to tell
you he was wrong.
There is only one:
"Who am I"?
Mr Parker.
Tardy again.
At least we can
always count on you.
Sorry, Miss Ritter, won't
happen again, I promise.
Don't make promises
you can't keep.
Yeah, but those are the best kind.
Okay, class, open your books.
Let's begin on page one.
Hello, doctor.
Did you tell the boy?
Tell him what?
Did you tell the boy the
truth about his father?
No.
Well, that's very good.
So we'll let him be for now.
You should leave him alone.